University Photograph; Collection ua390
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany's swim team about to enter the pool during a race., Undated
- A portrait of an unidentified member of the State University of New York at Albany's Women's swim team., Undated
- An unidentified member of the State University of New York at Albany's swim team diving into the pool., Undated
- A portrait of the unidentified former swim coach for the State University of New York at Albany's Women's swim team., Undated
- A team photograph of the State University of New York at Albany's Women's swim team., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany's swim team about to enter the pool during a race., Undated
- Former State University of New York at Albany's Women's coach, James Herrick., Undated
- Portrait of an unidentified member of the State University of New York at albany's Men's vollyball team., Undated
- Portrait of an unidentified member of the State University of New York at albany's Men's vollyball team., Undated
- Portrait of an unidentified member of the State University of New York at albany's Men's vollyball team., Undated
- Portrait of an unidentified member of the State University of New York at albany's Men's vollyball team., Undated
- Portrait of an unidentified member of the State University of New York at albany's Men's vollyball team., Undated
- Portrait of an unidentified member of the State University of New York at albany's Men's vollyball team., Undated
- Portrait of an unidentified member of the State University of New York at albany's Men's vollyball team., Undated
- An unidentified member of the State University of New York at Albany's swim team diving into the pool., Undated
- An unidentified member of the State University of New York at Albany's swim team diving into the pool., Undated
- An unidentified member of the State University of New York at Albany's swim team diving into the pool., Undated
- An unidentified member of the State University of New York at Albany's swim team diving into the pool., Undated
- Portrait of an unidentified member of the State University of New York at Albany's Women's tennis team., Undated
- Portrait of an unidentified member of the State University of New York at Albany's Women's tennis team., Undated
- Portrait of an unidentified member of the State University of New York at Albany's Women's tennis team., Undated
- Portrait of an unidentified member of the State University of New York at Albany's Women's tennis team., Undated
- Portrait of an unidentified member of the State University of New York at Albany's Women's tennis team., Undated
- Portrait of an unidentified member of the State University of New York at Albany's Women's tennis team., Undated
- Portrait of an unidentified member of the State University of New York at Albany's Women's tennis team., Undated
- Portrait of an unidentified member of the State University of New York at Albany's Women's tennis team., Undated
- Portrait of an unidentified member of the State University of New York at Albany's Women's tennis team., Undated
- Portrait of an unidentified member of the State University of New York at Albany's Women's tennis team., Undated
- Portrait of an unidentified member of the State University of New York at Albany's Women's tennis team., Undated
- Portrait of an unidentified member of the State University of New York at Albany's Women's tennis team., Undated
- A picture a member of the State University of New York at Albany gymnastics team performing on the balance beam., Undated
- An unidentified member of the State University of New York at Albany's swim team diving into the pool., Undated
- Portrait of an unidentified member of the State University of New York at Albany's Women's tennis team., Undated
- A group photograph of the State University of New York at Albany's Women's tennis team., Undated
- A group photograph of the State University of New york at Albany's Women's trck team., Undated
- A group portrait of the State University of New York at Albany gymnastics team., Undated
- A group portrait of unidentified cheerleaders of the State University of New York at Albany., Undated
- A group portrait of the State University of New York at Albany's women's tennis team., Undated
- A group portrait of the State University of New York at Albany's women's tennis team., Undated
- A group of unidentified participants of the State University of New York at Albany Alumni Association Board of Directors meeting., Undated
- An interior of an unidentified hall at the State University of New York at Albany., Undated
- Students on an athletic field behind the State University of New York at Albany's Alumni Quadrangle., Undated
- An interior of an unidentified hall at the State University of New York at Albany., Undated
- An exterior of an unidentified hall at the State University of New York at Albany., Undated
- A group of people gathered around tables during Community-University Day at the State University of New York at Albany in a building on the uptown campus. Written in the bottom margin is "122 Viscusi.", Undated
- A picture of John M. Sayles, Pd.B. (viewer's right), Acting President of the New York State College for Teachers from 1939-March 1, 1943 and President from March 1, 1943-March 10, 1947 and Milton G. Nelson, Ph.D. (viewer's left), Acting President, New York State College for Teachers from March 1947-July 1949. They are greeting students at a President's Reception., Undated
- A volunteer, Larry Pearson at the 1978 phonothon answering phones on the uptown campus of the State University of New York at Albany., Undated
- A volunteer, Michael Faber at the 1978 phonothon answering phones on the uptown campus of the State University of New York at Albany., Undated
- The 1978 phonothon volunteers anwsering phones in an unidentified classroom on the uptown campus of the State University of New York at Albany., Undated
- The 1978 phonothon volunteers anwsering phones in an unidentified classroom on the uptown campus of the State University of New York at Albany., Undated
- The 1978 phonothon volunteers anwsering phones in an unidentified classroom on the uptown campus of the State University of New York at Albany., Undated
- A picture of Helen G. Heikoff, State University of New York at Albany, Class of 1978, with a self portrait. There are crop marks on all sides of the photograph. In the bottom margin there are instructions to "reduce to 29p. x 20p." and there is a number 5 enclosed in a circle. Behind Ms. Heikoff is a painting of the Abstract Expressionist style., Undated
- State University of New York at Albany's Genevieve Moore presents the Sayles-Pierce Scholarships to students, Joyce Nicholls and Charkes Gibbs., Undated
- A portrait of Lorraine Theurer Brundage, New York State College for Teachers, Class of 1940., Undated
- A portrait of Edwin J. (Dr. E. J.) Holstein, New York State College for Teachers, Class of 1942., Undated
- A picture of Nancy Ann Baumann, State University of New York at Albany, Class of 1965., Undated
- A picture of Margaret F. Kurilecz, New York State College for Teachers, Class of 1933. At the time the photograph was taken, Ms. Kurilecz was in Athens, Greece as a Fulbright Scholar, 1954-1956. There are crop marks on all sides of the photograph., Undated
- Donald Mochon, founding director of the University Art Museum, University at Albany the first director of the Museum, from 1967 until 1976., Undated
- Former New York State Governor's wife Happy Rockefeller and former State University of New York at Albany president Evan R. Collins at an unidentified event., Undated
- A picture of Vincent O'Leary, Acting President from 1977?1978 and President from 1978?July 31, 1990 with a group of unidentified people dining. During O'Leary's administrations, the institution was named State University of New York at Albany from August 1962?fall 1986 and the University at Albany, SUNY starting in the fall of 1986 and continuing. O'Leary is the gentleman between the two women on the right side of the table. There are crop marks and in the top margin is written between arrows "55% 14 picas" and an uppercase letter "B" enclosed in a circle., Undated
- A picture of volleyball players in the middle of a game. In the right margin is written the name "David Asher," the photographer who made this picture and member of the State University of New York at Albany, Class of 1983 (BS) and University at Albany, SUNY, Class of 1987 (MS) and 1997 (MBA)., Undated
- E. Frances Thomson of the Student Personnel Department at the State University of New York at Albany., Undated
- Unidentified students sitting on the Academic Podium at the State University of New York at Albany., Undated
- A sign welcoming visitors to Community-University Day at the State University of New York at Albany on the uptown campus. The sign says "Community University Day: Saturday, OCT.7th, 10 to 5, Displays, Demonstrations, Films, Tours, Games, All Are Welcome." One of the quadrangles can be seen in the background., Undated
- Formal gardens behind the Campus Center on the Uptown Campus., Undated
- A picture of spectators with blankets and hot drinks in response to the cold weather associated with an outdoor event held on the State University of New York at Albany uptown campus. The spectators are probably attending a football game., Undated
- A picture of Tom Donelly in the midst of his campaign against littering. The image is from the student newspaper Carillon, April 1979. The activity is taking place on the Academic Podium of the uptown campus, State University of New York at Albany., Undated
- A picture of students (accompanied by a dog) engaging in leisurely activity on the lawn, which borders the traffic circle of the uptown campus. The traffic circle was renamed Collins Cirlce on June 8, 1991 in honor of Evan R. Collins, former President of the institution., Undated
- An unidentified female student reading a book on the Academic Podium at the State University of New York at Albany., Undated
- An unidentifed student playing pool in the Billiard Room at the State University of New York at Albany Campus Center. The photograph was taken eye-level with the pool table., Undated
- The Academic Podium including the water tower and State Quadrangle on the Uptown Campus., Undated
- Colonial Quadrangle and Social Science building from the Dutch Qaudrangle on the Uptown Campus., Undated
- Unidentified students on the stairs between the Indian Quadrangle to the Academic Podium at the State University of New York at Albany., Undated
- A group of unidentified students sitting on the lawn on one of the quadrangles at the State University of New York at Albany., Undated
- A high contrast photograph of two unidentified people standing on a staircase by the fountain on the Academic Podium of the State University of New York at Albany uptown Campus. The Campus Center and the moon can be seen in the background., Undated
- Unidentified students walking outside of a building on the uptown campus of the State University of New York at Albany., Undated
- A group of unidentified students gathered between the Humanities and Education buildings on the uptown campus at the State University of New York at Albany. There are corp marks in the left and bottom margins of the original., Undated
- A group of unidentified students sitting on the Academic Podium at the State University of New York at Albany on the uptown campus. Duplicate of image 4338., Undated
- Two unidentified students talking in front of the small fountain by the Campus Center at the State University of New York at Albany on the uptown campus., Undated
- Four unidentified students talking at the State University of New York at Albany on the uptown campus., Undated
- Unidentified students gathered on the Academic Podium at the State University of New York at Albany on the uptown campus. The original is mounted on a piece of matte board., Undated
- Two unidentified people, possibly students, sitting on benches in the formal garden behind the Campus Center at the State University of New York at Albany on the uptown campus., Undated
- View of the south side of the Physics and Chemistry Buildings as seen from the Campus Center deck, Uptown Campus., Undated
- Unidentified students on the Academic Podium near the Dutch Quadrangle. The original is mounted on a piece of matte board and has crop marks in the top, right, and bottom margins., Undated
- Unidentified students gathered around the small fountain outside of the Campus Center at the State University of New York at Albany uptown campus. The original is mounted on a piece of matte board., Undated
- View of the State University of New York at Albany's Uptown Campus in winter from the Dutch Quadrangle parking lot., Undated
- Unidentified students at typewriters in the Business Administration Building on the uptown campus at the State University of New York at Albany., Undated
- Unidentified students walking by a building on the Academic Podium at the State University of New York at Albany. There are crop marks in the top and bottom margins., Undated
- Unidentified students on the Academic Podium at the State University of New York at Albany uptown campus., Undated
- An unidentified male student sitting on the Academic Podium at the State University of New York at Albany uptown campus., Undated
- Unidentified students sitting on the Academic Podium at the State University of New York at Albany. The fountain can be seen in the background., Undated
- Unidentified students camping out at night on the Academic Podium at the State University of New York at Albany., Undated
- Unidentified students in the formal garden behind the Campus Center at the State University of New York at Albany on the uptown campus., Undated
- Unidentified students around the fountain outside of the Campus Center at the State University of New York at Albany uptown campus., Undated
- A photograph of Ethel Bicland, Edna Abbott, New York State College for Teachers, Class of 1926, Vinginia Baxter, Gertrude Cox, and Ruth Van Vlack., Undated
- Pictured in the front row are: Sheila M. Harrigan, State University of New York at Albany, Class of 1980, Laura L. Steib, State University of New York at Albany, Class of 1980, Elizabeth Colleran, and in the back row is Alan S. Waldman, State University of New York at Albany, Class of 1980., Undated
- Two unidentified female students walking on the uptown campus at the State University of New York at Albany., Undated
- Uptown Campus as viewed from the Dutch Quadrangle. Student Center in foreground, State Quadrangle in background., Undated
- Aerial view of the State University of New York at Albany's Uptown Campus., Undated
- Long shot of the Uptown Campus from the soccer field., Undated
- The Campus Center on the Uptown Campus., Undated
- A collection of portraits featuring (left to right, top to bottom) Oliver Arey, Principal of the (New York) State Normal School from December 2, 1864-January 8, 1867; Joseph Alden, President of the (New York) State Normal School from April 3, 1867-May 23, 1882; Edward P. Waterbury, A.M., Ph.D., President of the (New York) State Normal School from June 22, 1882-August 8, 1889; and William J. Milne, M.S., Ph.D., LL.D., President of the (New York) State Normal School (and then the New York State Normal College) from October 29, 1889-September 4, 1914. Each of the four photographs have the following descriptive information in the bottom margin(s): the gentleman's name, his title, and his dates of service., Undated
- A picture a member of the State University of New York at Albany gymnastics team performing on the balance beam., Undated
- A photograph of Edward L. Long, New York State College for Teachers, Class of 1917, and Chet Wood., Undated
- A portrait of Samuel B. Woolworth, LL.D., Principal of the (New York) State Normal School from September 20, 1852-February 1, 1856 and Acting Principal from Febrary 19, 1867-April 3, 1867. In the bottom margin is the caption, "SAMUEL B. WOOLWORTH, Principal 1852-1856.", Undated
- A portrait of John W. Jennings, New York State College for Teachers, Class of 1949. Jennings attended the college with the support of the GI Bill as a WWII Veteran. Jennings served as president of the Inter?Group Council, a local group advocating better racial and religious relations. It is believed that Jennings was the first African American president of the Student Council, also called the Student Association., Undated
- Major Frederick W. Crumb, New York State College for Teachers, Class of 1930 and World War II veteran. During the war, Crumb served in the Education Branch, Moral Services Division in Army Service Forces., Undated
- A group of unidentified female students at the New York State College for Teachers sitting on the lawn and reading a newspaper. This image appeared in the Pedagogue., Undated
- Yellowstone fields research, in the back row is Vincent Schaefer, Larry Proctor, Dr. Dale Hartlieb, August Auer, Griffith Morgen, John Stockner, and Austin Morgen. On the bottom row is Dr. Richard Layton, Charles Robertson, Thomas Henderson, John Hirsch, and Robert Smith Johnson., Undated
- A picture of Sanford Zimmerman, former owner of Cohoes (NY) Specialty Stores Ltd. and Senior Assistant to Karen Hitchcock, former University at Albany, SUNY President. Zimmerman was a visiting speaker to the university., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- Unidentified members of the State University of New York at Albany community during an unidentified event., Undated
- A contact sheet displaying images of Senator Daniel Patrick Moynihan delivering a speech in the Performing Arts Center. Moynihan served in the U.S. Senate from New York as a Democrat from 1977-2001., Undated
- A contact sheet displaying images of Senator Daniel Patrick Moynihan. Moynihan served in the U.S. Senate from New York as a Democrat from 1977-2001. He spoke in the Performing Arts Center., Undated
- A contact sheet displaying images of Senator Daniel Patrick Moynihan. Moynihan served in the U.S. Senate from New York as a Democrat from 1977-2001. He spoke in the Performing Arts Center., Undated